Guide to the Kiwanis Club of Houston records, 1919-2017 MS 619
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Projects and Fund Raisers, 182198
  - Project: Briarwood School, 183585
    - Project: Briarwood School file, 1980-1981; 182284 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Project: Houston Job Fair, 183586
    - Project: Houston Job Fair file, 1970; 182285 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Project: Texas Crime Prevention Association, 183587
    - Project: Texas Crime Prevention Association file, 1977-1978; 182286 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Project: Texas Army/Alamo, 183588
    - Project: Texas Army/Alamo file, 1977-1982; 182287 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Project: Blue Bonnet Bowl, 183589
    - Project: Blue Bonnet Bowl file, 1984; 182288 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Project: Ronald McDonald House, 183590
    - Project: Ronald McDonald House file, 1983-1984; 182289 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Project: Speech and Hearing Institute, 183591
    - Project: Speech and Hearing Institute file, 1972-1982; 182290 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Project: Race for Life, 183592
    - Project: Race for Life file, 1981; 182291 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Project 30, 183593
    - Project 30 file, 1980-1981; 182292 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Project: Clarewood House Golden K, 183594
    - Project: Clarewood House Golden K file, 1977; 182293 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Project: Living Bank, 183595
    - Project: Living Bank file, 1977; 182294 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Project: Blue Bonnet Bowl, 183596
    - Project: Blue Bonnet Bowl file, 1976; 182295 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Project: US Navy Band, 183597
    - Project: US Navy Band file, 182296 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Plan Haiti Project, 183598
    - Plan Haiti Project file, 182297 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Children of Panama Fund Drive, 183599
    - Children of Panama Fund Drive file, 182298 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Christmas in June, 183600
    - Christmas in June file, 2009; 182299 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Miracle Network Telethon, 183601
    - Miracle Network Telethon file, 182300 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Million Dollar Foundation Fund Drive, 183602
    - Million Dollar Foundation Fund Drive file, 182301 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Galleria Chamber of Commerce, 183603
    - Galleria Chamber of Commerce file, 182302 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Health Awareness Week, 183604
    - Health Awareness Week file, 1982; 182303 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Winifred Hirsch Sweetheart Celebration, 183605
    - Winifred Hirsch Sweetheart Celebration file, 1989; 182304 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Sweet Heart Celebration, 183606
    - Sweet Heart Celebration– Holsey/Custom Tailors List, 1989; 182305 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Sweet Heart Celebration- Custom Tailors and Designers Association of America Membership Roster, 988; 182306 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Sweet Heart Celebration Finances, 1989, 182307 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Sweet Heart Celebration Ephemera, 182308 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Sam Houston Birthplace Marker, 183607
    - Sam Houston Birthplace Marker file, 1986; 182309 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Sam Houston Birthplace Marker Plans, 1986; 182310 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - General Sam Houston Memorial, 182311 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Series IV: Club Finances, 182312
  - Monthly Reports, 183608
    - Monthly Reports, 1948-1949; 182313 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Monthly Reports, 1949-1950; 182314 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Monthly Reports, 1950-1951; 182315 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Monthly Reports, 1951-1952; 182316 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Monthly Reports, 1952-1953; 182317 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Monthly Reports, 1953-1954; 182318 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Monthly Reports, 1954-1955; 182319 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Monthly Reports, 1955-1956; 182320 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Monthly Reports, 1956-1957; 182321 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Monthly Reports, 1957-1958; 182322 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Monthly Reports, 1958-1959; 182323 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Monthly Reports, 1959-1960; 182324 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Monthly Reports, 1960-1961; 182325 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Monthly Reports, 1961-1962; 182326 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Monthly Reports, 1962-1963; 182327 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Monthly Reports, 1963-1964; 182328 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Monthly Reports, 1964-1965; 182329 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Monthly Reports, 1965-1966; 182330 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Monthly Reports, 1966-1967; 182331 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Monthly Reports, 1967-1968; 182332 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Monthly Reports, 1968-1969; 182333 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Monthly Reports, 1969-1970; 182334 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Monthly Reports, 1970-1971; 182335 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Monthly Reports, 1971-1972; 182336 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - Monthly Reports, 1972-1973; 182337 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Monthly Reports, 1973-1974; 182338 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Monthly Reports, 1974-1975; 182339 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Monthly Reports, 1975-1976; 182340 (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - Monthly Reports, 1976-1977; 182341 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - Monthly Reports, 1977-1978; 182342 (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - Monthly Reports, 1978-1979; 182343 (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Monthly Reports, 1979-1980; 182344 (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Monthly Reports, 1980-1981; 182345 (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - Monthly Reports, 1981-1982; 182346 (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - Monthly Reports, 1982-1983; 182347 (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - Monthly Reports, 1983-1984; 182348 (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - Monthly Reports, 1984-1985; 182349 (Box 13, Folder 74)
    - Monthly Reports, 1985-1986; 182350 (Box 13, Folder 75)
    - Monthly Reports, 1986-1987; 182351 (Box 13, Folder 76)
    - Monthly Reports, 1987-1988; 182352 (Box 13, Folder 77)
    - Monthly Reports, 1988-1989; 182353 (Box 13, Folder 78)
    - Monthly Reports, 1990-1991; 182354 (Box 13, Folder 79)
    - Monthly Reports, 1999-2000; 182355 (Box 13, Folder 80)
    - Monthly Reports, 2000-2001; 182356 (Box 13, Folder 81)
    - Monthly Reports, 2001-2002; 182357 (Box 13, Folder 82)
    - Monthly Reports, 2002-2003; 182358 (Box 13, Folder 83)
    - Monthly Reports, 2003-2004; 182359 (Box 13, Folder 84)
    - Monthly Reports, 2004-2005; 182360 (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Ledgers, 183609
    - Ledgers, 1972-1973; 182361 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Ledgers, 1972-1974; 182362 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Ledgers, 1974-1975; 182363 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Ledgers, 1975-1976; 182364 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Ledgers, 1976-1977; 182365 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Ledgers, 1977-1978; 182366 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Ledgers, 1978-1979; 182367 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Ledgers, 1979-1980; 182368 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Ledgers, 1980-1981; 182369 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Ledgers, 1981-1982; 182370 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Ledgers, 1982-1983; 182371 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Ledgers, 1984-1985; 182372 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Ledgers, 1985-1986; 182373 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Ledgers, 1989-1990; 182374 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Ledgers, 1987-1994; 182375 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Ledgers, 1995-1999; 182376 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Disbursements and Receipts, 183610
    - Disbursements and Receipts, 1938-1940; 182377 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Disbursements and Receipts, 1941-1947; 182378 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Disbursements and Receipts, 1944-1947; 182379 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Disbursements and Receipts, 1947-1949; 182380 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Disbursements and Receipts, 1949-1951; 182381 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Disbursements and Receipts, 1952-1953; 182382 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Disbursements and Receipts, 1954-1955; 182383 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Disbursements and Receipts, 1956-1957; 182384 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Disbursements and Receipts, 1958-1959; 182385 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Disbursements and Receipts, 1960-1961; 182386 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Disbursements and Receipts, 1962-1963; 182387 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Disbursements and Receipts, 1964-1965; 182388 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Disbursements and Receipts, 1966-1967; 182389 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Disbursements and Receipts, 1968-1969; 182390 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Disbursement Journal, 1969-1970; 182391 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Disbursement Journal, 1970-1971; 182392 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Disbursement Journal, 1971-1972; 182393 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Disbursement Journal, 1973-1976; 182394 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Disbursement Journal, 1977-1980; 182395 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Disbursement Journal, 1980-1994; 182396 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Receipts Journal, 1972-1978; 182397 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Achievement Reports, 183611
    - Achievement Reports, 1930s; 182398 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Achievement Reports and Subcommittee Budgets, 1943-1950; 182399 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Achievement Reports (1 of 2), 1940s; 182400 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Achievement Reports (2 of 2), 1940s; 182401 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Achievement Reports (1 of 2), 1950s; 182402 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Achievement Reports (2 of 2), 1950s; 182403 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Achievement Reports (1 of 2), 1960s; 182404 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Achievement Reports (2 of 2), 1960s; 182405 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Achievement Reports, 1970s; 182406 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Annual Club Reports, 183612
    - Annual Club Reports, 1970s; 182407 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Annual Club Reports, 1980s; 182408 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Annual Club Reports, 1990s; 182409 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - R.B. Pearson- Quarterly Report to Sponsoring Club Downtown Houston Kiwanis, 182410 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Audit Reports, 183613
    - Audit Report, 1931; 182411 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Audit Report, 1933; 182412 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Audit Report, 1934; 182413 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Audit Report, 1935; 182414 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Audit Report, 1936; 182415 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Audit Report, 1937; 182416 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Audit Report, 1938; 182417 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Audit Report, 1939; 182418 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Audit Report, 1941; 182419 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Audit Report, 1944; 182420 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Audit Report, 1945; 182421 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Audit Report, 1946; 182422 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Audit Report, 1949; 182423 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Audit Report, 1950; 182424 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Audit Report, 1951; 182425 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Audit Report, 1954; 182426 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Audit Report, 1955; 182427 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Audit Report, 1956; 182428 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Audit Report, 1957; 182429 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Audit Report, 1958; 182430 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Audit Report, 1959; 182431 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Audit Report, 1960; 182432 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Audit Report, 1961; 182433 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Audit Report, 1962; 182434 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Audit Report, 1963; 182435 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Audit Report, 1965-1966; 182436 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Audit Report, 1977; 182437 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Audit Report, 1979-1980; 182438 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Bank Statements, 183614
    - Bank Statements, 1980-1981; 182439 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Bank Statements, 1981-1982; 182444 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Bank Statements, 1987-1988; 182445 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Bank Statements, 1988-1989; 182446 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Bank Statements, 1989-1990; 182447 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Bank Statements, 1990-1991; 182448 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Bank Statements, 1991-1992; 182449 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Bank Statements, 1992-1993; 182450 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Bank Statements, 1993-1994; 182451 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Bank Statements, 1994-1995; 182452 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Bank Statements, 1995-1996; 182453 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Bank Statements, 1996-1997; 182454 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Bank Statements, 1997-1998; 182455 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Bank Statements, 1998-1999; 182456 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Bank Statements, 1999-2000; 182457 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Bank Statements, 2000-2001; 182458 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Bank Statements, 2001-2002; 182459 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Bank Statements, 2002-2003; 182460 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Bank Statements, 2003-2004; 182461 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Frost Bank, 2004; 182462 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Frost Bank Authorized Signors, 2000; 182463 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Frost Bank Account Statement, 1999-2004; 182464 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Cash Disbursements by Budget Accounts, 183615
    - Cash Disbursements by Budget Accounts, 1951; 182465 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Cash Disbursements by Budget Accounts, 1952; 182466 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Cash Disbursements by Budget Accounts, 1953; 182467 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Cash Disbursements by Budget Accounts, 1954; 182468 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Cash Disbursements by Budget Accounts, 1955; 182469 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Cash Disbursements by Budget Accounts, 1956; 182470 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Cash Disbursements by Budget Accounts, 1957; 182471 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Cash Disbursements by Budget Accounts, 1958; 182472 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Cash Disbursements by Budget Accounts, 1959; 182473 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Cash Disbursements by Budget Accounts, 1960; 182474 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Cash Disbursements by Budget Accounts, 1961; 182475 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Cash Disbursements by Budget Accounts, 1962; 182476 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Cash Disbursements by Budget Accounts, 1963; 182478 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Cash Disbursements by Budget Accounts, 1964; 182479 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Statement of Cash Receipts and Disbursements and Accountants' Opinion, 1964; 182480 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Budget Accounts, 1966; 182481 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Cash Disbursements by Budget Accounts, 1967; 182482 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Cash Disbursements by Budget Accounts, 1968; 182483 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Cash Disbursements by Budget Accounts, 1969; 182484 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Cash Disbursements by Budget Accounts, 1969-1970; 182485 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Cash Disbursements by Budget Accounts, 1970-1971; 182486 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Club Checking Account, 1994-2000; 182487 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Register and Balance Sheets, 183616
    - Register and Balance Sheets, 8-9/1994; 182488 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Register and Balance Sheets, 1994-1995; 182489 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Month end close out- club accounts, 1995; 182490 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Register and Balance Sheets, 1995-1996; 182492 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Register and Balance Sheets, 1996-1997; 182493 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Register and Balance Sheets, 1997-1998; 182494 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Register and Balance Sheets, 1998-1999; 182495 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Register and Balance Sheets, 1999-2000; 182496 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Register and Balance Sheets, 2000-2001; 182497 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Register and Balance Sheets, 2001-2002; 182499 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Register and Balance Sheets, 2002-2003; 182500 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Register and Balance Sheets, 2003-2004; 182501 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Register and Balance Sheets, 2004-2005; 182502 (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Register and Balance Sheets, 2005-2006; 182503 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 10/2006; 182504 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 11/2006; 182505 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 12/2006; 182506 (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 1/2007; 182508 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 2/2007; 182509 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 3/2007; 182510 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 4/2007; 182512 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 5/2007; 182513 (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 6/2007; 182514 (Box 18, Folder 72)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 7/2007; 182515 (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 8/2007; 182516 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 9/2007; 182517 (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 10/2007; 182518 (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 11/2007; 182519 (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 12/2007; 182520 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 1/2008; 182521 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 2/2008; 182522 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 3/2008; 182523 (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 4/2008; 182524 (Box 18, Folder 82)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 5/2008; 182528 (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 6/2008; 182529 (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 7/2008; 182530 (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 8/2007; 182532 (Box 18, Folder 86)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 9/2007; 182533 (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 10/2007; 182534 (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 11/2007; 182535 (Box 18, Folder 89)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 12/2007; 182536 (Box 18, Folder 90)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 1/2008; 182544 (Box 18, Folder 91)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 2/2008; 182545 (Box 18, Folder 92)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 3/2008; 182546 (Box 18, Folder 93)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 4/2008; 182547 (Box 18, Folder 94)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 5/2008; 182548 (Box 18, Folder 95)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 6/2008; 182549 (Box 18, Folder 96)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 7/2008; 182550 (Box 18, Folder 97)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 9/2008; 182552 (Box 18, Folder 98)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 10/2008; 182553 (Box 18, Folder 99)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 11/2008; 182554 (Box 18, Folder 100)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 12/2008; 182555 (Box 18, Folder 101)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 1/2009; 182556 (Box 18, Folder 102)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 2/2009; 182557 (Box 18, Folder 103)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 3/2009; 182558 (Box 18, Folder 104)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 4/2009; 182559 (Box 18, Folder 105)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 5/2009; 182560 (Box 18, Folder 106)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 6/2009; 182561 (Box 18, Folder 107)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 7/2009; 182562 (Box 18, Folder 108)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 8/2009; 182563 (Box 18, Folder 109)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 9/2009; 182564 (Box 18, Folder 110)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 10/2009; 182565 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 11/2009; 182566 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 12/2009; 182567 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 1/2010; 182573 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 2/2010; 182574 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 3/2010; 182575 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 4/2010; 182576 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 5/2010; 182577 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 6/2010; 182578 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 7/2010; 182579 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 8/2010; 182580 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Register and Balance Sheets and Bank Records, 9/2010; 182581 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Budgets, 183651
    - Estimated Budget, 1965; 182582 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Office Supplies and Printing Budget, 1972-1973; 182583 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Budget Work Sheets, 1969-1976; 182584 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Budget, 1976-1977; 182585 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Budget, 1977-1978; 182586 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Budget and Supporting Materials, 10/1978-9/1979; 182587 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Budget and Supporting Materials, 1979-1980; 182588 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Budget Ledger, 1988-1989; 182589 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Budget Ledger, 1989-1990; 182590 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Budget Ledger, 1990-1991; 182591 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Budget Ledger, 1991-1992; 182592 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Budget Ledger, 1992-1993; 182593 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Proposed Budget, 1984-1995; 182594 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Budgets, Operating Statements, and Supporting Materials, 1993-1994; 182595 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Budgets, Operating Statements, and Supporting Materials, 1994-1995; 182596 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Budgets, Operating Statements, and Supporting Materials, 1995-1996; 182597 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Budgets, Operating Statements, and Supporting Materials, 1996-1997; 182598 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Budgets, Operating Statements, and Supporting Materials, 1997-1998; 182599 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Budgets, Operating Statements, and Supporting Materials, 1998-1999; 182600 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Budgets, Operating Statements, and Supporting Materials, 1999-2000; 182602 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Budgets, Operating Statements, and Supporting Materials, 2000-2001; 182603 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Budgets, Operating Statements, and Supporting Materials, 2001-2002; 182604 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Budget, 2002-2003; 182605 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Operating Statements, and Supporting Materials, 2003-2004; 182606 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Budgets, Operating Statements, and Supporting Materials, 2004-2005; 182607 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Budget, 2005-2006; 182608 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Budget, 2007-2008; 182609 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Assorted Financial Records, 183654
    - General Journal, 1972-1973; 182610 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Disbursements Journal, 1972-1973; 182611 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Ledger Book- Donations(?), 1973-1974; 182612 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Money Management/ IRA's, 1988-1991; 182613 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Money Market Account, 1992-1996; 182614 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Money Market Account, 1996-1997, 2001; 182615 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - United Bank, 182616 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Statements SG Cowen Securities, 1994-1998; 182617 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - PMT Register, 2000; 182618 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Miscellaneous Tax Correspondence, 5/2006; 182619 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Sales Tax exemption- Circuit City, 182620 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Finance and Budget Committee, 1954; 182621 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Resolutions to Govern Handling of Account, 1980-1989; 182622 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Insurance, 182623 (Box 19, Folder 53)
- Series V: Awards, 182624
  - Awards File, 182625 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Bush Awards, 183669
    - Bush Award- Banking, 182626 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Bush Award Recipients, 182628 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Bush Award (1 of 2), 2002; 182629 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Bush Award (2 of 2), 2002; 182630 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Bush Award, 2003; 182631 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Bush Award (1 of 2), 2004; 182632 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Bush Award (2 of 2), 2004; 182633 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Bush Award, 2005; 182634 (Box 20, Folder 3)